{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "000000001",
            "category": 1,
            "question": "Assume a variable <code>x</code> with a value of <code>[0,0,0,0]</code> exsists. Identify which choice causes an error.",
            "choices": [
                "<code>x[1]&#160;=&#160;1</code>",
                "<code>x[2]&#160;=&#160;2</code>",
                "<code>x[3]&#160;=&#160;3</code>",
                "<code>x[4]&#160;=&#160;4</code>"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "id": "000000002",
            "category": 2,
            "question": "Which loop is guaranteed to run at least one time?",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>repeat</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>for</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>while</code>",
                "None of the Above"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }, 
        {
            "id": "000000003",
            "category": 2,
            "question": "Which loop can be used for iterating over arrays?",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>for</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>while</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>repeat</code>",
                "All of the Above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "id": "000000004",
            "category": 3,
            "question": "Which data type should you use with decimal numbers in Swift?",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>Float</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>Double</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>Int</code>",
                "All of the Above"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "id": "000000005",
            "category": 4,
            "question": "Which access control modifier is the most restrictive?",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>public</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>private</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>internal</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>fileprivate</code>"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "id": "000000006",
            "category": 0,
            "question": "Given the parameter int is an Integer and given str is a String, which function will prints the two values concatenated together?",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>func&#160;concatenate(int:&#160;Int,&#160;str:&#160;String)&#160;{&#160;print(\"\\(int)\"&#160;+&#160;str)&#160;}</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>func&#160;concatenate(int:&#160;Int,&#160;str:&#160;String)&#160;{&#160;print(int&#160;+&#160;str)&#160;}</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>func&#160;concatenate(int:&#160;Int,&#160;str:&#160;String)&#160;{&#160;print(\"(int)(str)\")&#160;}</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>func&#160;concatenate(int:&#160;Int,&#160;str:&#160;String)&#160;{&#160;print(int.append(str))&#160;}</code>"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "id": "000000007",
            "category": 0,
            "question": "Which of the following is not a boolean?",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>true</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>false</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>nil</code>",
                "All are booleans"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "id": "000000008",
            "category": 1,
            "question": "What is the type of the following variable? <code>var&#160;fruits&#160;=&#160;[\"Watermelon\",&#160;\"Mango\",&#160;\"Apple\"]</code>",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>[String]</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>[Int]</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>[Double]</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>[Bool]</code>"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "id": "000000009",
            "category": 1,
            "question": "What is index <code>1</code> of the following array? <code>var&#160;fruits&#160;=&#160;[\"Watermelon\",&#160;\"Mango\",&#160;\"Apple\",&#160;\"Orange\"]</code>",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>\"Apple\"</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>\"Watermelon\"</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>\"Mango\"</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>\"Orange\"</code>"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "id": "000000010",
            "category": 1,
            "question": "Which of the following types is this array? <code>[nil,&#160;nil,&#160;,&#160;nil,&#160;45,&#160;nil,&#160;13,&#160;46,&#160;nil]</code>",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>[Int?]</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>[[Int]?]</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>[String?]</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>[Bool?]</code>"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "id": "000000011",
            "category": 1,
            "question": "Which of the following statements are true? Assume <code>var&#160;array&#160;=&#160;[4,&#160;8,&#160;7,&#160;6,&#160;5,&#160;4,&#160;3,&#160;2,&#160;0,&#160;8,&#160;9]</code>",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>array[0]&#160;==&#160;7</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>array[3]&#160;==&#160;0</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>array[2]&#160;==&#160;3</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>array[10]&#160;==&#160;9</code>"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "id": "000000012",
            "category": 1,
            "question": "Which of the following arrays have only one element?",
            "choices": [
                "<code style='color: green;'>[]</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>[1,2]</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>[[\"Hello\",&#160;\"Thanks\",&#160;\"Goodbye\"][0]]</code>",
                "<code style='color: green;'>[[1][0],&#160;1]</code>"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}